Guide to the Larry Rivers Papers 1952-2010 MSS 293
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series XIII: Personal Files
  - [Political Advocacy], 1985-88, undated (Box 101, Folder 42)
  - Postcards, undated (Box 101, Folder 43)
  - Recreational Concepts (pool maintenance), 1999 (Box 101, Folder 44)
  - Sam Rivers, 1995, undated (Box 101, Folder 45)
  - RESTRICTED - Sam Rivers - Student Records, 1985-98, undated (Box 101, Folder 46)
  - RESTRICTED - Sam Rivers - Student Records, 1986-96, undated (Box 101, Folder 47)
  - RESTRICTED - Sam Rivers - Student Records, 1995, undated (Box 101, Folder 48)
  - RESTRICTED - Sam Rivers - Student Records, 1996-2000, undated (Box 102, Folder 1)
  - RESTRICTED - Sam Rivers - Student Records, 1998-2001 (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - RESTRICTED - Sam Rivers - Student Records, undated (Box 102, Folder 3)
  - [Signature Book from Rivers's Birthday Party], 1995 (Box 102, Folder 4)
  - Steven Rivers, 1980-93, undated (Box 102, Folder 5)
  - RESTRICTED - Steven Rivers - Student Records, 1959-1961 (Box 102, Folder 6)
  - RESTRICTED - United Nations International School, 1992 (Box 102, Folder 7)
  - RESTRICTED - Walden School, 1973 (Box 102, Folder 8)
  - [Yiddish Practice], 1995, undated (Box 102, Folder 9)
- Series XIV: Audio
  Series XIV: Audio contains audio cassettes and reels.
  Audio items were given unique IDs in their original order. Unique titles are based upon annotations on original items and their containers. Alternate titles are offered where multiple titles were implied by container annotations, or in the case of uniform titles for series of items.
  Preservation work has not been performed on these items, and therefore they may not be available for access. Please contact the Fales Media Archivist for more information.
  - Tits, undated (Box 154, Media ID: 293.1169)
    Format: 1/4 in. reel to reel
    TRT:
  - Interview and Music, undated (Box 154, Media ID: 293.1170)
  - [Pygmy Mwami], undated (Box 154, Media ID: 293.1171)
    Alternate Title:
    Pygmie
  - Unknown, undated (Box 154, Media ID: 293.1172)
  - L.R. Speech, undated (Box 154, Media ID: 293.1173)
  - Man, undated (Box 154, Media ID: 293.1174)
  - Unknown, undated (Box 154, Media ID: 293.1175)
  - Some American History I, undated (Box 154, Media ID: 293.1176)
    AM History
  - Some American History II, undated (Box 154, Media ID: 293.1177)
  - Some American History III, undated (Box 154, Media ID: 293.1178)
  - Some American History IV, undated (Box 154, Media ID: 293.1179)
  - Songs by John Gruen, Feb 1963 (Box 154, Media ID: 293.1180)
  - [Messy Lives - Frank O'Hara], undated (Box 154, Media ID: 293.1181)
    Messy Lives
  - Native Son, undated (Box 154, Media ID: 293.1182)
  - [Africa Reel 1], undated (Box 154, Media ID: 293.1183)
    Gaisseau - Africa
  - [Africa Reel 2], 21 Feb 1968 (Box 154, Media ID: 293.1184)
    Adv. Club
  - Wini Sync, undated (Box 154, Media ID: 293.1185)
  - [Lampman, Tits], undated (Box 154, Media ID: 293.1186)
    L. Man Master
  - [Some American History], undated (Box 154, Media ID: 293.1187)
    J. Bruch
  - [1st part, Arnold & L.R.], undated (Box 154, Media ID: 293.1188)
    Arnold & L.R.
  - [John Gruen, Soni Stoye], undated (Box 154, Media ID: 293.1189)
    John Gruen
  - [John Gruen #2], undated (Box 154, Media ID: 293.1190)
  - Slave Ship Sounds, undated (Box 154, Media ID: 293.1191)
  - [Lynn in bath, Penny dancing, Lynn answers telephone], undated (Box 154, Media ID: 293.1192)
    Lynn in Bath
  - [KT-C, Toronto], undated (Box 154, Media ID: 293.1193)
    KT-C
  - [Big Brown spot], undated (Box 154, Media ID: 293.1194)
    Big Brown
  - [Soni Stoye], undated (Box 154, Media ID: 293.1195)
    Soni
  - [Arnold Weinstein & Larry Rivers], undated (Box 154, Media ID: 293.1196)
    Arnold Weinstein
  - [Master Holly at Pool Table], Mar 4 1971 (Box 154, Media ID: 293.1197)
    Pool Table
  - [Andy Warhol, Bridget Polk], undated (Box 154, Media ID: 293.1198)
    Andy Warhol
  - [Andy Warhol, John Gruen], undated (Box 154, Media ID: 293.1199)
  - [Bridget Polk & Andy Warhol], undated (Box 154, Media ID: 293.1200)
  - [Andy & Bridget Polk with Larry], undated (Box 154, Media ID: 293.1201)
    Andy & Bridget Polk
  - Unknown, undated (Box 154, Media ID: 293.1202)
  - Unknown, undated (Box 154, Media ID: 293.1203)
  - Unknown, undated (Box 154, Media ID: 293.1204)
  - [Tits - Dave], undated (Box 154, Media ID: 293.1205)
    Tits
  - Clarice Tits, undated (Box 154, Media ID: 293.1206)
  - [Tits - Amy & Celea], undated (Box 154, Media ID: 293.1207)
  - Interview, undated (Box 154, Media ID: 293.1208)
  - Interview, undated (Box 155, Media ID: 293.1209)
  - Interview, undated (Box 155, Media ID: 293.1210)
  - Unknown, undated (Box 155, Media ID: 293.1211)
  - Turkana, undated (Box 155, Media ID: 293.1212)
    Unknown
  - [Congo Music/Black is Black], undated (Box 155, Media ID: 293.1213)
    Congo Music
  - [Masai Griaha], undated (Box 155, Media ID: 293.1214)
    MA SAI
  - [Masai], undated (Box 155, Media ID: 293.1215)
  - [Masai], undated (Box 155, Media ID: 293.1216)
  - [Brown], undated (Box 155, Media ID: 293.1217)
  - [Nairobi, Safariland, Opening], undated (Box 155, Media ID: 293.1218)
    Africa Tapes
  - [Elephant, Yusef & Road Signs], undated (Box 155, Media ID: 293.1219)
  - [Tree Tops Side I], undated (Box 155, Media ID: 293.1220)
  - [Tree Tops II, Elephants sounds], undated (Box 155, Media ID: 293.1221)
  - [Dream], undated (Box 155, Media ID: 293.1222)
  - [Nightmare, Lampman & Rivers], undated (Box 155, Media ID: 293.1223)
  - A Monk in the Country, 20 Dec 1989 (Box 155, Media ID: 293.1224)
    Format: 2 in. reel to reel
  - Blues for Bob/Take a Half Step, 20 Dec 1989 (Box 155, Media ID: 293.1225)
    Blues for Bob
  - Strange Enchantment, 20 Dec 1989 (Box 155, Media ID: 293.1226)
  - [Unknown Audio Tape], undated (Box 155, Media ID: 293.1227)
  - Rivers, 7 Jan 1979 (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1228)
    Format: Audiocassette
  - Lukas Foss, undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1229)
  - [Olsen I, Baby], undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1230)
    Olsen I
  - Larry Rivers III, undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1231)
  - Louis & Mary Poiner on Rivers, undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1232)
  - Climax Band, undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1233)
  - Rivers #4, undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1234)
  - [Evander Childs High School/Harlem Hospital], undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1235)
    Evander Childs High School #23
  - Pearlstein on Painting, Sep 18 1982 (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1236)
  - [False Vagina: Liz & Lee, Second Session], undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1237)
    Liz - Lee False Vagina
  - [Philadelphia Spectrum Set II], Apr 6 1982 (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1328)
    Philadelphia Set II
  - [L.R. Auto-Bio Interview, Radio San Francisco], Oct 30 1992 (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1237)
    L.R. Auto Bio Interview
  - Elanie De Kooning, Jun 4 1988 (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1240)
  - Strand, Lyceum London, May 26 1972 (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1241)
  - [Liz - Lee - Tony], undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1242)
    Liz - Lee Tony IIC
  - Unknown, undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1243)
  - Lee Krasner #8, undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1244)
  - [Climax Band], undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1245)
    Climax
  - [Auto-Bio S.H. in the '50s], undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1246)
    Auto Bio #1
  - [Jack Freilicher], undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1247)
    Augusta
  - [Thanksgiving 1991], Nov 1991 (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1248)
    Thanksgiving
  - Larry R. Reviewing 1946,47,48, undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1249)
  - [Harold Rosenberg #26 and #27A], undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1250)
    Harold Rosenberg
  - Brofsky - Rivers, undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1251)
  - Pete Calandra, undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1252)
  - Climax Band, undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1253)
  - [Mike Burstyn: Yiddish Songs/Andy Statman: Klezmer Orchestra], undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1254)
    Mike Burstyn
  - [Phoebe & Larry at "Cocos"], [Feb 1983] (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1255)
    Phoebe & Larry
  - [4-Track Recording - Climax Band], 1992 (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1256)
    Climax Band
  - [Studio Museum/Parsons School], undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1257)
    Studio Museum
  - [Larry Rivers Band at Quantuck Beach Club], Aug 12 1994 (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1258)
    L.R. Band at Quantuck
  - Climax Band, undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1259)
  - Unknown, undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1260)
  - [Dexter Gordon/Heath, Brofsky & Dexter], undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1261)
    Dexter Gordon
  - [WPA part II], undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1262)
    WPA 10
  - Unknown, undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1263)
  - Jack Freilicher, undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1264)
  - [13 Standards Part II], undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1265)
    13 Standards
  - Joe Henderson - Double Rainbow, undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1266)
    Joe Henderson
  - [East 13th Street Jazz], 11 Jun 1981 (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1267)
    East 13th St. Band
  - Hirshhorn, 1983 (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1268)
  - Sonya Chamina: Russian Gypsy Songs, undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1269)
    Sonya Chamina
  - Larry & Steve, undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1270)
  - Larry Rivers Program 18:00-20:00, Dec 9 1985 (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1271)
    L.R. Program at Tac
  - [Harlem Hospital, Dorothy Daner], undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1272)
    Harlem Hospital
  - Turkish Karsilama, undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1273)
  - WPA 1, undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1274)
  - East 13th Street Band, Dec 28 1982 (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1275)
  - [MT Verdi], undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1276)
    Verdi
  - Unknown, undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1277)
  - Larry Rivers, Aug 2 1978 (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1278)
  - ["The Book" on Jazz - Courbet/Larry and Phoebe - "No PLace for Truth in Show Biz"], undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1279)
    The Book on Jazz
  - The Uman Jazz Unit: Wheel of Time, undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1280)
    Uman Jazz Unit
  - [[Star of David] 9], undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1281)
  - [[Star of David] 10], undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1282)
  - Unknown, undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1283)
  - Rorem, undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1284)
  - Me, undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1285)
  - [KALX - 90.7 FM, Berkeley, CA], Oct 29 1997 (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1286)
    KALX FM
  - [Arnie's Band - Deanna's], May 19 1994 (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1287)
    Arnie's Band
  - Bob Keene, undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1288)
  - Unknown, undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1289)
  - Larry Rivers Program 16:00-17:30, 9 Dec 1985 (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1290)
  - [Sequential 1946], undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1291)
  - Climax Band Demo Tape, undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1292)
  - [Larry Rivers (Sax) Altos De Chavon], undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1293)
    Larry Rivers Sax
  - [Interview of Rivers by a Japanese Critic], undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1294)
    L.R. Interview Japanese Critic
  - [Larry 1946-47 & Other Things], undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1295)
    Larry 1946-47
  - Johnny Morris, undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1296)
  - [Pete Calandra, String Quartet], undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1297)
    Pete Calandra
  - Climax Band, undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1298)
  - Climax Band, undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1299)
  - [Pete Calandra "Fox" Promos], undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1300)
    Calandra
  - NPR Interview with Larry Rivers, Apr 25 1999 (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1301)
  - Unknown, undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1302)
  - Climax Band, undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1303)
  - [Eddy Grant, Ronnie Laws], undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1304)
    Ronnie Laws
  - [Rivers tape #8], undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1305)
    Rivers
  - [Joni & East 13th Street Band: Summer Time], undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1306)
    Joni & E 13th St. Band
  - [Moscow-Leningrad], undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1307)
    Washington Trip
  - University Lecture L.R. and Nathan Joseph, undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1308)
  - [Mahagonny/Tit Contest], undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1309)
    Tit Contest
  - Golden Bough Hospital, undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1310)
  - Unknown, undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1311)
  - [Beethoven's Ninth], undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1312)
  - [L.R. on Hofmann/Al Kresch], undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1313)
    L.R. on Hofmann
  - Rehearsal, undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1314)
  - Larry Rivers, undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1315)
  - Sonia, undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1316)
  - O'Connors #6, undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1317)
  - [Speak No Evil/Sphere - Bird Calls], undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1318)
    Shorter
  - [History 1 On 1/Rain for the Heat], 1985 (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1319)
    History 1 on 1
  - Hazens - Jane, undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1320)
  - Broadcast of Dec. 17, 1992 (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1321)
  - Chicago News Conference, undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1322)
  - [Abolafia Phone/Rose Rubin], undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1323)
    Abolafia
  - [Rerecords], undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1324)
    Prince, Steve
  - Superbitch, undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1325)
  - Unknown, undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1326)
  - [Satie Music], undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1327)
    Satie
  - Conversation Bridget, undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1328)
  - Unknown, undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1329)
  - [Larry Rivers Lecture, Hirshhorn], Jul 16 1981 (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1330)
    Rivers Hirshhorn
  - [Female Jazz Singing - Aretha?], undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1331)
    Jazz Singing
  - Camp - Larry Musical, undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1332)
  - [S-M], undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1333)
  - [Clarice, Typed], undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1334)
    Clarice
  - [Lamp/Jackie], undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1335)
    Lamp
  - [Abbie Riff with College [?]], undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1336)
    Abbie
  - [Olsen typed], undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1337)
    Olsen
  - Rivers #C7, undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1338)
  - [Ricardo + L'il Darlin], undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1339)
  - [Big Brown/Holly Taylor], undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1340)
  - Steven, Winnie, undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1341)
  - Arnold Cooper, undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1342)
  - Maureen, undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1343)
  - Grey Gallery, undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1344)
  - [L.R. & H.B. Acroama], Jan 6 1986 (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1345)
    LR & HB
  - [Larry & Ed Gordon etc. - Buying Building], undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1346)
    Larry & Ed Gordon
  - [John Gruen, Larry, Bonnie, Amy, Celea, Soni, Lynn], undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1347)
    John Gruen, Larry
  - [Michael Newell, Dorothy Miller], undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1348)
    WPA Dorothy Miller
  - Unknown, undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1349)
  - False Vagina: Kelly & Liz, undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1350)
  - Unknown, undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1351)
  - W.P.A. Symposium at Loeb, Dec 1977 (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1352)
  - Hoosiers Suzanne, undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1353)
  - Mahagonny, undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1354)
  - Unknown, undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1355)
  - [13th St. Band, 5/24, 25 - 1984 Unmixed Tape 1], May 24-25 1984 (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1356)
    13th St. Band
  - Diana, undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1357)
  - Unknown, undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1358)
  - [Wild Sound, Larry & Diana], undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1359)
    Larry & Diana
  - [Joe et al], undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1360)
    Joe
  - [Lee Krasner, tape 7 part 1], undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1361)
    Lee Krasner
  - [ E 13 St Band 5/24, 25 1984 Unmixed, Tape 2], undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1362)
    E. 13th. St. Band
  - [Music Minus One, 17 Standards #2], undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1363)
    Music Minus One
  - [Tucky], undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1364)
    4
  - [Don Cherry], undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1365)
  - [Museum/Bowling], undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1366)
    Museum
  - Broadcast of Dec. 17, 1992 (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1367)
  - [David & Larry, Art], undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1368)
    David & Larry
  - Rivers #3, #4, undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1369)
  - Rivers #7, undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1370)
  - 4 Nurses of the Apocalypse, 1995 (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1371)
  - [Monk w/Griffin & Lockjaw], undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1372)
  - [Pavarotti & Sutherland], undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1373)
  - [Pep Shop Boys/Herman Brood], undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1374)
  - [Gustav Mahler Symphony No. 2 "Resurrection"], 1977 (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1375)
  - [Classical/Merry Christmas Mr. Lawrence], undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1376)
  - [Practice Tape], undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1377)
  - [Beethoven], undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1378)
  - [Bob Marley/Al Green], undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1379)
  - [Charles Mingus], undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1380)
  - [Third World/Bill Withers, Rickie Lee, TAJ, Coleman & Hawkins, Fats], undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1381)
  - [Happy Birthday Joan], undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1382)
  - [Acid Jazz], undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1383)
  - [Beethoven Sonatas], undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1384)
  - [90s Contemporary Dance Not Retro!!!/Electronics to TechnoPop to 80's Pop], undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1385)
  - [Beethoven Sonata for Piano & Cello], undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1386)
  - [Jobim/Classical], undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1387)
  - Jingle Bells, undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1388)
  - Larry Rivers and the Climax Band, undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1389)
    Format: CD-R
  - Larry Rivers Climax Band, undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1390)
  - Unknown, undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1391)
  - [Long IS nu.], undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1392)
  - Phoebe Legere, undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1393)
  - [Calandra- Music], undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1394)
  - Pete Calandra, Nov 30 2001 (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1395)
  - Pete Calandra, undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1396)
  - [Pete Calandra NBC Olympic Show], undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1397)
  - [Larry Rivers Climax Band], undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1398)
  - [John Patton - Boogaloo Boogie], 1995 (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1399)
    Format: CD
  - [Everything - Larry Rivers], undated (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1400)
  - [Larry Rivers Interview, Lana Jokel], Dec 17 1991 (Box 156, Media ID: 293.1405)
  - Tits DAT from 16mm Composite Print, undated (Box 157, Media ID: 293.1732)
    Format: DAT
  - John Ashbery - "De Chirico," Poetry Project, NYC, March 1979 (Box 157, Media ID: 293.1733)
    TRT: approx. 120 minutes
  - [Unknown], undated (Box 157, Media ID: 293.1747)
    Format: Microcassette
    TRT: approx. 30 minutes
  - "Rave 'Til Dawn / "The movement 'Jump', 2 Unlimited 'Get ready for this", undated (Box 157, Media ID: 293.1748)
    TRT: approx. 90 minutes
  - Interview - English and French, undated (Box 157, Media ID: 293.1749)
    TRT: approx. 60 minutes
    Scope and Content:
    Annotation on tape label: "I can't ID the people on tape"
  - Christmas, 1991 (Box 157, Media ID: 293.1750)
  - Henny Youngman, undated (Box 157, Media ID: 293.1751)
    TRT: [approx. 30 minutes]
  - Some Music - Not LR, undated (Box 157, Media ID: 293.1752)
  - Grateful Dead - Toronto 6/21/84, 1984 (Box 157, Media ID: 293.1753)
  - WBLS Mix, undated (Box 157, Media ID: 293.1754)
  - Little Charlie and the Nightcats Pt 2, undated (Box 157, Media ID: 293.1755)
  - Stones / Bowie, Station to Station, undated (Box 157, Media ID: 293.1756)
  - Danny Wright, undated (Box 157, Media ID: 293.1757)
  - Laurie Anderson: Home of the Brave / Joe Cocker: With a Little Help from My Friends, undated (Box 157, Media ID: 293.1758)
  - [Mixtape], undated (Box 157, Media ID: 293.1759)
    Label annotations illegible.
  - Summer Groove, undated (Box 157, Media ID: 293.1760)
  - Muse, Rockabilly, undated (Box 157, Media ID: 293.1761)
    TRT: approx. 100 minutes
  - [Chess Records], undated (Box 157, Media ID: 293.1762)
  - Jazz Mixed... S. Vaughn, Satin Doll, undated (Box 157, Media ID: 293.1763)
  - Holiday 97, 1997 (Box 157, Media ID: 293.1764)
    Cassette Annotation: "With Love, Gospel + Blues + Mambo + More, Louis Armstrong, Ray Charles, Nina Simone"
  - Vangelis: "China", undated (Box 157, Media ID: 293.1765)
    TRT: approx. 46 minutes
  - Spanish Music, undated (Box 157, Media ID: 293.1766)
    TRT: unknown
  - Rivers 11/17 #8, undated (Box 157, Media ID: 293.1767)
  - The Matrix, San Francisco, Halloween 1968, undated (Box 157, Media ID: 293.1768)
    Tracklist: A: "Darkstar, Death Letter Blues, Lovelight, Jam, Drumz" B: "Drumz, The Other One, Death Don't Have No Mercy, with Marvin Harmonica Jam, Walkin' Cane"
  - Make Believe Ballroom, Great American Music Hall, San Francisco, 8/13/75, 1985 (Box 157, Media ID: 293.1769)
    Tracklist: A: "Help on the Way -> Slipknot -> Franklins Tower, The Music Never Stopped, Eyes of the World, King Solomon's Marbles, Stronger than Dirt" B: "It Must Have Been, The Roses, Round and Round, Sugare, Big River, Goin' Down the Road"
  - Paladins, undated (Box 157, Media ID: 293.1770)
  - Satyagraha, undated (Box 157, Media ID: 293.1771)
    Annotations: Side A: "Sade - Love de-lux", Side B: [illegible] - Merengue - Venezuela"
  - Minnie's Mix, undated (Box 157, Media ID: 293.1772)
  - Strange Enchantment, 1989 (Box 157, Media ID: 293.1773)
    Format: Magnetic Track
  - [Reel 1], undated (Box 157, Media ID: 293.1774)
  - [Reel 2], undated (Box 157, Media ID: 293.1775)
  - [Unknown], undated (Box 157, Media ID: 293.1776)
  - [Unknown], undated (Box 157, Media ID: 293.1777)
  - [Unknown], undated (Box 157, Media ID: 293.1778)
  - [Unknown], undated (Box 157, Media ID: 293.1779)
  - [Unknown], undated (Box 157, Media ID: 293.1780)
  - [Unknown], undated (Box 157, Media ID: 293.1781)
- Series XV: Film
  Series XV: Film contains film reels, primarily 16mm acetate film.
  Films were given unique IDs in their original order. Unique titles are based upon annotations on original items and their containers. Alternate titles are offered where multiple titles were implied by container annotations, or in the case of uniform titles for series of items.
  Preservation work has not been performed on these items, and therefore they not be available for access. Please contact the Fales Media Archivist for more information.
  - Africa Workprint Reel 1, undated (Media ID: 293.1406)
    Gauge: 16mm
    Footage: [800 ft]
    Color; silent.
    [Africa]
  - Africa Workprint Reel 2, 1968 (Media ID: 293.1407)
    Africa A2
  - Africa Workprint Reel 3, 1968 (Media ID: 293.1408)
    Africa A3
  - Africa Workprint Reel 4, Jan 30 1968 (Media ID: 293.1409)
    Footage: [1200 ft]
    Africa A4
  - Africa Workprint Reel 5A, 1992 (Media ID: 293.1410)
    Footage: [1450 ft]
  - Africa Workprint Reel 5B, 1992 (Media ID: 293.1411)
    Footage: [670 ft]
  - Africa Workprint Reel 6, undated (Media ID: 293.1412)
    Footage: [950 ft]
  - Africa Workprint Reel 7, Dec 6 1967 (Media ID: 293.1413)
    Footage: [1400 ft]
  - Africa Workprint Reel 8, undated (Media ID: 293.1414)
    Footage: [700 ft]
    Africa A8
  - Africa Workprint Reel 9, Jan 30 1968 (Media ID: 293.1415)
    Footage: [1100 ft]
  - Africa Workprint Reel 10, undated (Media ID: 293.1416)
  - Africa Workprint Reel 11, Dec 11 1967 (Media ID: 293.1417)
    Footage: [1300 ft]
    Color;silent.
  - Africa Workprint Reel 12, undated (Media ID: 293.1418)
    Africa A12
  - Africa Workprint Reel 13, undated (Media ID: 293.1419)
    Africa A13
  - Africa Workprint Reel 14, undated (Media ID: 293.1420)
    Footage: [1350 ft]
    Africa A14
  - Africa Workprint Reel 15, Dec 7 1967 (Media ID: 293.1421)
    Africa A15
  - Africa Workprint Reel 16, undated (Media ID:293.1422)
    Footage: [1430 ft]